Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Paul Ehrlich papers
1954-2001
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Ehrlich, Paul R.
SC0223
54.5 Linear Feet
Correspondence, memos, notes, photographs, posters and other papers relating to Paul Ehrlich's publications and public appearances, his work with the Rocky Mountain Biological Laboratory, Jasper Ridge Biological Presrve (California), the Zero Population Growth organization, and the Stanford Biological Sciences Department. Correspondents include Norman Cousins, J. Gordon Edwards, Sol Encel, Erich Fromm, Jane Goodall, Daniel McKinley, Margaret Mead, Lawrence Lader, E. C. Pielou, Eliot Porter, and Jonas Salk. Collection also includes materials relating to Dr. Anne Ehrlich's biological research and videotape of Paul Ehrlich's appearance on the Tonight Show.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Paul R. and Anne Ehrlich, 1980-2001.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Paul R. Ehrlich is Professor of biology at Stanford (1959- ) and is presently Bing Professor of Population Studies; Anne Ehrlich is a Research Assistant in the Biology Department at Stanford.
Description of the Collection
Correspondence, memos, notes, photographs, posters and other papers relating to Paul Ehrlich's publications and public appearances, his work with the Rocky Mountain Biological Laboratory, Jasper Ridge Biological Presrve (California), the Zero Population Growth organization, and the Stanford Biological Sciences Department. Correspondents include Norman Cousins, J. Gordon Edwards, Sol Encel, Erich Fromm, Jane Goodall, Daniel McKinley, Margaret Mead, Lawrence Lader, E. C. Pielou, Eliot Porter, and Jonas Salk. Collection also includes materials relating to Dr. Anne Ehrlich's biological research and videotape of Paul Ehrlich's appearance on the Tonight Show.
Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve (Calif.); Photoprints.; Videorecordings.; Biological research.; Biology.; Posters.; Population policy.; Notes.; Kornberg, Arthur; Dahlberg, Kenneth A.; Dalrymple, Dana G.; Cloud, Preston Ercelle; Cousins, Norman.; Ford, E. B. (Edmund Brisco); Forbes, William Trowbridge Merrifield; Enke, Stephen.; Encel, Sol.; Ehrlich, Paul R.; Ehrlich, Paul R.; Ehrlich, Anne H.; Edwards, J. Gordon.; Goodall, Jane; Odum, Eugene Pleasants; Mead, Margaret; Salk, Jonas; McKinley, Daniel.; Porter, Eliot; Lader, Lawrence.; Pielou, E. C.; Zero Population Growth.; Klots, Alexander B. (Alexander Barrett); Voevodsky, John.; Van Den Bosch, Robert.; Fromm, Erich; Stanford University. Department of Biology; Rocky Mountain Biological Laboratory
- General Files and Correspondence, Series 1
  - Environmental Studies at Stanford (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Union - U.S.E. - 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Moulton, Robert H., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Humanities - Sears, Hastorf, Carnochan, 1965-75 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Glover, Frederic O., 1970-75 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Miller, William, V-P and Provost, 1974-78 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Massy, William (V-P for Research), research development fund, 1971-76 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - President Lyman, 1968-78 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pirages-Ehrlich Social Ecology Program, 1971-72 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Academic Council, Commission on the professoriat at Stanford, 1971-72 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University Operating Budget Guidelines for 1973-74, 1975-76 [empty] (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Committee for the program in human biology, Oct. 1969 - July 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Computer accounts after 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Typing - to 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Jasper Ridge subcommittee of the departmental policy committee, 1971-78 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Director of graduate studies, 1974-75 (meeting folder) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Director of graduate studies 1974 (1972-75) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stanford press releases prior to 1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NSF senior postdoctoral fellowship award file (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Requests for candidates, 1970-75 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - PRE - student expenses, estimates 1-6/72 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Inquiries about graduate and postgraduate work at Stanford, 1969-75 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Requests for identification letters for field trips; insurance for vehicle, 1967-72 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Human biology information, 1971-72 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Franklin Counsel fund and etc. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Journal of International Studies, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Biology Study Group "The Destruction of Indochina," 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Time required for Ph.D. at Stanford (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Edge - Ken Cooper, 1977-79 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Freshman seminar committee, 1968-70 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Freshman seminars, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Committee on student evaluation of teaching, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - SCORE - Student competitions on relevant engineering (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - SCIRE, 1972-78 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Life science for Vietnam (3/24/71) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - M.R. Buma - accounting office 1974 (1975) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Stanford University, general correspondence, 1958-1975 (emphasis 1958-59) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - General Secretary's Office (Helen Shepard), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research. Massy, Brest, 1972-73 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Committee on biocide use (1971-72) and Committee on biohazard control 1974 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Sponsored Projects office, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Student employment policies, 1973-74 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - The future of man seminars, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Departmental seminars 1972-73, 1973-74, 1975-76 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Seminar speakers - 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - "Information - seminar speaker" forms (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Lasta Pomacavoch - urban studies - ZPG 1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - SWOPSI - 1977-78 - Hansch, hunger (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - U.R.P. - summer 1974 (Undergraduate Research Program biology dept.) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Jobseekers 1975 and on (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Persons interested in faculty positions (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Common Cause (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Photographs [relocated to Series 9 Audio-Visual Materials, Box 1] (Box 5)
  - Guest book (boxed) (Box 5)
  - Career summary (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Australia (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Expenses and receipts (summer 1966) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Receipts for purchases (sabbatical) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Equipment (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Field trip expenses, Papua, New Guinea, November 4 - December 15 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Expense reports, August 1965 - July 1966 (sabbatical) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Expenses July 14 - July 23 - Kenya and Tanzania (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Expenses June 23 - July 14, 1966 - Thailand, Cambodia, and India (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Expenses, Malawi - Rhodesia July 23, 1966 - August 17, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Expenses: Sydney, Alice Springs, Darwin - May 17 - 22, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Malaysian expenses May 22 - June 23, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Field trip expenses - South Australia Jan. 11 - Feb (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Field trip expenses, July 4 - Sept. 24, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Information for vitas (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Mailing schedule - May 9 to Sept. 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - C.C. Chua (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Society dues paid for 1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NSF senior postdoctoral fellowship (final report) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NSF postdoctoral applications (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Expenses - Summer 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Expenses - Summer 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Expenses - Summer 1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Expenses - Summer 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Expenses - Summer 1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Expenses - Summer 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Expenses - Summer 1962 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Expenses - Summer 1961 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Expenses - Summer 1960 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Research Plans (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sabbatical General (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Flying (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Insect-plant correspondence (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Insect-plant study (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Preliminary list of butterflies dissected (empty)] (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Figs from systematic zoology ??????? (empty) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lima - November 1974 [See also Kellock, Antarctica] (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Costa Rica: December 10, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - List of possible collectors; regional list of genera; directions for preserving (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - McGovern, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Justin Blackwelder - before 1972 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Charles Birch - before 1972 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Env. directory (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - PBGF permissions (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - PBGF - contribs & fees, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Autographed photos of Pre (letters) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Ernst, Jeff, and Paul letters (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Growald (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Misc. Endorsements and requests (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Form letters re: one dimensional ecology (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlet: one dimensional ecology (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions for equipment purchased on grants (old), 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions - stamps 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Motter Bookbinders and Stanford Press Bindery 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Subscriptions - requisitions 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Typists 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Requisitions - Office supplies, 1972-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Requisitions - Services and equipment, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Address lists, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Requisitions - Books not from bookstore, 1972-1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Bookstore Orders PBGF, 1971-1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Answers to Inquiries, Forms of response - 70's (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dental X-rays, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Odetics, inc. Joel Slutsky time lapse video recorder, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Colorblindness, contact lens, etc., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Recruitment of Black students, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Statements re. genocide, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Subject List for newspaper clipping, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Subject Headings (for filing of reprints), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Directory of the Population-related Community in Wash. DC Area, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Letters from/to Welton L. Lee, 1/26/68 re. meeting at ???????, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Population/Food fund consultant's roster, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Mag.: Sci. Institute pub. info, June 1977 (Box 9)
  - State Graduate Fellowships, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Entomological Collections, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Pamphlet: Eco-Catastrophe, by Dr. Paul Ehrlich, Sept. 1969 (Box 9)
  - Paper: The Food from the Sea Myth, by Dr. Paul Ehrlich, April, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence: Ehrlich to A. Tratner/Environmental Educ. Group, 11/72 (Box 9)
  - Pamphlets:
    - Statistics re. emissions (Box 9)
    - Question on Prop 9 (Box 9)
    - Nuclear Power & Ecocide, 1974 (Box 9)
    - People's Action Research, 1972 (Box 9)
    - The Coming Ecological Catastrophe (Box 9)
    - Environmental Action Directory, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Statistics on Bay Area Growth: 50's, 60's, 70's (Box 9)
    - Environmental Task Force (Box 9)
  - Correspondence:
    - from Stewart L. Udall (Box 9)
    - from Science Amer. Assoc. for the Advancement of Science, 1972 (Box 9)
    - from Nick Pole: Transport Research Project, 8/27/72 (Box 9)
    - Danlere trip, 10/72 (Box 9)
  - Faculty Political Action Group, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Visiting Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Subcommittee on Admissions; Graduate Admissions Reports: 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1975-76 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Subcommittee on Master's, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ASSU Course Guide, 12/79 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Grant Applications, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Undergraduate Studies Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Untitled: Consists of correspondence form high school students in Iowa who need the Population Bomb, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Asking for Organizations, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - No title: contains misc. hand-outs & brochures detailing bibliographies (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Persons interested in graduate study (population), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Persons interested in undergraduate study (population), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Persons interested in employment (population), 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous odd letters to Paul, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Information: environment (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Environment colleges placement service (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Job requests, 1972-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fellow workers, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mailing List: Job and Guidance Seekers, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Long Bibliography Requests, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Job seekers, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Letters of Appreciation and Thanks, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Script and Paper requests, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Print & reprint requests, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Print & reprint requests, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Letters with Ideas and Information, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Letters with Ideas and Information, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Letters with Ideas and Information, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Letters with Ideas and Information, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Letters with Ideas and Information, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pre: Selected Bibliographies, various n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Donation/Payment Acknowledgement, 1975-76 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Chronological File, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chron. File: Jan. - Jun. 1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chron. File: July - December 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Chron. File: 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Harriman File, 1971 (Paul Ehrlich's Exec. Assistant) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Pole, Nicholas: 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ron Dellums Endorsement, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Forum for Contemporary History, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - George McGovern, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - American College Lecture Bureau (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Political Endorsements 1970, 1971, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Reviews Refused, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Statements against Prop. 17 (death penalty) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Pat Ferraro, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lilenthal Programs, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Speeches Bureau, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Program Corporation of America, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Harry Walker, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Chron. File - Letters, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Population Institute: Telethon, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sierra Club, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Form Letters (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Volunteers, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Bryson, R. A. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Chamberlain - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Hartman, Ilka - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Havlick, Spenser - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - LaPollette, Doug - 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Stewart R. Mott - 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Burton G. Ross, St. Paul, Minn. - 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Stern, Robert D. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Advertising and the Environment (pamphlet) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Beverage, container ???? (pamphlet) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Carpooling (pamphlet) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Environmental Organizations (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - The Advocates (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Audobon Society (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - California Journal (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Common Cause, 1971-72 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Documentary Film Co., 1974 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - IPPF News, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - NON (National Organization for Non-Parents), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Oceanic Society, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Organic Gardening (Rodale), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence File A-D, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence File E-I, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence File, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence File R-Z (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - 4th Estate B-Copy Clippings (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Pamphlets, Articles, and Correspondence: (Box not specified)
  - Pollution, 1970,s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pesticides, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Food, 1967-1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Climate, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Solar Energy, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - War, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Opinions, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Curricula, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Abortion - Catholic - St. Thomas Aquinas, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Abortion - General, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ants, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Energy, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Phosphate Analyses Notes on Pollution, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Fisheries, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fluoridation, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Mirex - Fire Ant Campaign, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Oil Leak, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - CA. Bureau of Land Management, Off Road Vehicle Plan., UC Berkeley Committee, Zoologogy Dept., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - (Population Control, not named by Ehrlich) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - (Population Control, not named by Ehrlich) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - (Population Control, not named by Ehrlich) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - (Population Control), 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Overpopulation, 1960-1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Congress on Optimum Population and Environment, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - COPE - Board of Directors (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: T, 1972-75 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: U, 1972-74 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: V, 1972-75 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: W, 1972-75 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: X,Y,Z 1971-73 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Paul Ehrlich [Correspondence 1969-1979] (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Responses, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Incoming, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Responses, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Incoming, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Incoming, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Responses, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Incoming, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Catholics & Religious Objectors, Responses, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 12 year old letters (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, World Federalists Party (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, W., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, P, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, B, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, D, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, E, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, L, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, N, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, P, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, R, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, W, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, A, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, B, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, C, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, E, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, F, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, G, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, H, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, I, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, J, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, K, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, L, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, M, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, N, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, P, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, R, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, S, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, T, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, V, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, W, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, Y, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, January 1968 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, February 1968 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, March 1968 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, April 1968 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, May 1968 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, June 1968 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, July 1968 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, August 1968 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, September 1968 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, October 1968 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, November 1968 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, December 1968 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, A, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, B, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, C, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, D, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, E, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, F, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, G, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, H, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, J, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, L, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, M, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, N, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, O, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, P, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, Q, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, R, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, S, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, U, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, V, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, W, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, January 1967 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Febraury 1967 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, March 1967 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, April 1967 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, May 1967 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, June 1967 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, July 1967 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, August 1967 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, September 1967 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, October 1967 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, November 1967 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, December 1967 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A- (1970) (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, B 1970 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, C-D 1970 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, E-F 1970 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, G-H 1970 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, J-K 1970 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, L-M 1970 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, N-R 1970 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, S 1970 (Box 22, Folder 84)